OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Are you nervous?
緊張してます?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Try taking a deep breath.
深呼吸をしてみてください
Have you calmed down?
落ち着いた?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
It's difficult, isn't it?
難しいよね
What are you doing now?
今、何してる人ですか?
I'm currently attending university.
今、大学に通ってます
What university?
何大学ですか?
何大学なの?
I go to a regular university.
普通の大学に通ってます
I don't understand difficult things.
難しいことは分かんないんです
That's what I'm going to do now.
今からやることさ
yes.
はい
can.
できる
Something naughty.
やらしいこと
Have you ever done something naughty?
やらしいこと、したことあるでしょう?
It won't happen.
なりないです
And now,
ですし、もう、
good.
いい
How many people have you dated?
何 人くらいと付き合ったことある?
Until now, there has only been one person.
今までは、 一人だけです
How many people have experience?
経験人数も?
Many people are also one.
多数の人も一人です
Can you do it today?
今日、できる?
When was the last time you did it?
最近、したのはいつ?
Not at all, like many years ago.
全然、もう、何年も前とか
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くないか?
Does it hurt?
痛いか
Did it hurt the first time you did it?
初めてやったときは、痛かった?
It hurt just a little.
ちょっとだけ、痛かったです
Did you get any salt?
塩は出た?
It might have come out already.
もう、出たかもしれない
Can I see your panties?
パンツ見せてもらっていいですか?
Yeah.
うん
Did you show me your pants?
パンツ見せた?
Is it now?
今ですか?
difficult?
難しい?
It's difficult.
難しいです
Don't you ever show me those pants?
そんなパンツ見せることないの?
No.
ないです
Yeah.
うん
Is that it?
それですか?
Do you usually wear something like this?
普段、こんなの履いてるの?
No, I don't usually wear them.
いや、 いつもは、履いてないです
It's like a rail, so I bought it earlier.
レール的だから、 さっき買って、
I've been wearing them.
履いてきました
It's like this.
こんな感じ
It hurts.
痛いです
It was reflected.
映っちゃいましたね
Look at something.
何かを見て
Can I say something naughty again?
また、やらしいこと言っていいですか?
What is it?
なんですか?
Can I see something?
何かを見ていいですか?
It's difficult.
難しいです
Is it okay to watch?
見るのはいいですか?
No, it's difficult.
いや、難しい
I don't know.
わかんないね
difficult.
難しい
It's difficult.
難しいです
Are you going home directly?
直接帰るんですか?
that's right.
そうです
taking a bath
お風呂入
Will you come?
って きます?
I'm going to take a bath.
お風呂入ってきます
Were you showing me your pussy?
まんこさ、見せてた?
I've always wanted to see this.
ずっと見たがるからね、これ
why?
なんで?
Properly.
ちゃんと
oh
お
I took a bath.
風 呂入ってきました
I'm going to give your pussy a bath.
まんこの風呂入れるから
Feet this way.
足こっちを
oh yeah.
そうそう
Take it yourself.
自分で持って持って
Try it in.
入 れてみて
Try moving it yourself.
自分で動かしてみる
Can't move?
動けない?
Did you notice something was served?
何か出されたのが分かった?
It felt good, right?
気持ちよかったでしょう?
How was it?
どうかった?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?